// const btn = document.querySelector(#a)const arr = [
    const arr = [{
        question: 'Which of these phrases means "Bewakoof Banana"?',
        a: "Jhoote Phekna",
        b: "Topi Pahnana",
        c: "Note Lahrana",
        d: "Upvaas Karna",
        correct: "Topi Pahnana",
        money: "1,000",
    },
    {
        question: '"Kanya Pujan is a ritual associated with which Hindu festival',
        a: "Gangaur",
        b: "Navratri",
        c: "Hartalika Teej",
        d: "Ahoi Asthanmi",
        correct: "Navratri",
        money: "2,000",
    },
    {
        question: "With which part of a computer is the advertising slogan 'Intel Inside' associated",
        a: "BIOS",
        b: "RAM",
        c: "USB",
        d: "Processor",
        correct: "Processor",
         money: "5,000",
    },
    {
        question: "Mithila and Madhubani are also names of which kind of folk art",
        a: "Embroidery",
        b: "Handicraft",
        c: "Folk songs",
        d: "Painting",
        correct: "Painting",
         money: "10,000",
    },
     {
        question: "Muammar Gaddafi was the ruler of which country from 1969 to 2011?",
        a: "Libya",
        b: "Syria",
        c: "Sudan",
        d: "Egypt",
         correct: "Libya",
         money: "20,000",
    },
     {
        question: "Karnataka, one of the southern states of India, was known by which of these names before being renamed in 1973?",
        a: "Khandesh",
        b: "Mysore",
        c: "Coorg",
        d: "Madurai",
         correct: "Mysore",
         money: "40,000",
    },
     {
        question: "After their meeting at Ashoka Vatika, what object did Devi Sita give to Lord Hanuman to take to Lord Rama?",
        a: "Her necklace",
        b: "Her anklet",
        c: "Her hair ornament",
        d: "A piece of cloth",
         correct: "Her hair ornament",
         money: "80,000",
        },
      {
        question: "In which of these continents bats are not found",
        a: "Africa",
        b: "Australia",
        c: "South America",
        d: "Antarctica",
          correct: "Antarctica",
         money: "1,60,000",
        },
       {
           question: "In which of these positions did Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel not serve in the first cabinet of independent India?",
           
        a: "Deputy Prime Minister",
        b: "Minister of Information",
        c: "Minister of Defence",
        d: "Minister of Home Affairs and State",
        correct: "Minister of Defence",
         money: "3,20,000",
    },  
    { 
        question: "The desktop application of which web browser will be retired and will go without support from June 2022",
        a: "Opera",
        b: "Firefox",
        c: "Safari 14",
        d: "Internet Explorer",
        correct: "Internet Explorer",
         money: "6,40,000",
        },
    {
        question: "Which of the following dynasties did the Kanva dynasty overthrow to come to power around 73 BCE in Magadha?",
        a: "Maurya Dynasty",
        b: "Shunga Dynasty",
        c: "Pala Dynasty",
        d: "Cheera Dynasty",
        correct: "Shunga Dynasty",
        money: "12,50,000",
        },
    {
        question: "The trophy which is awarded to the winners of the women's singles at the Australian Open is named after which legendary tennis star?",
        a: "Daphne Akhurst",
        b: "Margaret Court",
        c: "Evonne Goolagong Cawley",
        d: "Lessley Bowery",
        correct: "Daphne Akhurst",
         money: "25,00,000",
        },
        {
        question: "Who became the first Chancellor of the ALigarh Muslim University in 1920?",
        a: "Sultan Jahan Begum",
        b: "Maulana Abdul Kalam Azad",
        c: "Sir Syed Ahmad Khan",
        d: "Mir Usman Ali Khan",
        correct: "Sultan Jahan Begum",
        money: "50,00,000",
        },
      {
          question: "Who is the first woman and also former astronaut to reach the deepest point of the ocean , Mariana Trench?",
          a: "Sally Ride",
        b: "Valentina Tereshkova",
        c: "Svetlana Savitskaya",
        d: "Kathryn D Sullivan",
        correct: "Kathryn D Sullivan",
         money: "1 Crore",
        },
       {
           question: "Where in Singapore dod Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose make the first proclamation of a Azad Hind government?",
        a: "Cathy Cinema Hall",
        b: "Fort Canning Park",
        c: "National University of Singapore",
        d: "National Gallery Singapore",
        correct: "Cathy Cinema Hall",
        money: "7 Crore",
    }, 
];
const que=document.querySelector(".ques");
const op1=document.querySelector("#opt1");
const op2=document.querySelector("#opt2");
const op3=document.querySelector("#opt3");
const op4=document.querySelector("#opt4");
const options=document.querySelectorAll(".options");
const contain = document.querySelector(".contain");
const win = document.querySelector(".win");
const lf1 = document.querySelector("#lf1");
const lf2 = document.querySelector("#lf2");
const lf3 = document.querySelector("#lf3");
const clue = document.querySelector(".clue");
const btn = document.querySelector(".btn");
const on = document.querySelector(".on");

    
const circle = document.querySelector(".circle");
const money = document.querySelector(".money");



 money.style.display = "none";
    win.style.display = "none";
    circle.style.display = "none";
contain.style.display = "none";



  var audio = new Audio('KBC.mp3');
  
  
  const onn = document.querySelector(".onn");
const quit = document.querySelector(".quit");



on.addEventListener('click', () => {
    setTimeout(() => {
        
        money.style.display = "flex";
       win.style.display = "flex";
       // win.style. ="center";
       circle.style.display = "flex";
       contain.style.display = "flex";
       on.style.display = "none";
       onn.style.display = "none";
       // playAudio("KBC.mp3");
         audio.play();
     audio.loop = true;
    }, 800);
})
    

    let score = 0;
    let i = 0;
function loadquiz() {

    
    que.innerHTML = arr[i].question;
    op1.innerHTML = arr[i].a;
    op2.innerHTML = arr[i].b;
    op3.innerHTML = arr[i].c;
    op4.innerHTML = arr[i].d;
}

function moneys() {
    money.innerHTML = "₹ "+ arr[i].money;
}

// ad.style.display="none";
function show() {
    contain.innerHTML = `<h2>Congratulations</h2>
    <p><h1>You won :${score}</h1></p>
    <p><button class="btn" onclick="location.reload()" style="width:174px; margin:15px;cursor:pointer;font-size:26px; border-radius:4px;"> Play Again </button></p>`;
    contain.style.backgroundColor = "gold";
    contain.style.height = "400px";
     contain.style.width = "600px";
    contain.style.color = "black";
    contain.style.fontSize = "30px";
    contain.style.margin = "10px";
    // muted('KBC.mp3');
    audio.muted = true;
  
    money.style.display = "none";
    win.style.display = "none";
    circle.style.display = "none";
    
    
   

    
}
quit.addEventListener('click', () => {
    setTimeout(() => {
        
        show();
    }, 600);
})
for(item of options){
    item.addEventListener('click', function (e) {
        buttonText = e.target.innerText;
        
        
        
        if (buttonText == arr[i].correct) {
            score = "₹ "+arr[i].money;
            
            setTimeout(()=>{
                e.target.style.background = "green";
                
                win.innerText = `You won: ${score}`
                
                // console.log(score);
                
                
            }, 200)
            
            
            setTimeout(() => {
                i++;
                
                if (i < arr.length) {
                    
                    decolor();
                    moneys();
                    loadquiz();
                    
                    
                    if (i <= 3) {
                        
                        circle.innerHTML = 30;
                        timer = 30;
                        clearInterval(interval);
                    }
                    else if (i > 3) {
                        
                        circle.innerHTML = 45;
                        timer = 45;
                        clearInterval(interval);
                    }
               
                    
                }
                else {
                    
                    
                    

                    show();
        }
    }, 1000);
    
 
        
            
}
else {
            setTimeout(()=>{
                e.target.style.background = "red";
                
                
                 }, 200)
            setTimeout(() => {
                if (i < 3)
                    score = "₹ " + "0" ;
                    
                    else if (i > 3 && i < 8)
                        score = "₹ " + "10, 000";
                    else if (i > 8)
                    score = "₹ " + "3,20,000" ;
                    show();
                    win.style.background = "black";
                win.style.color = "black";
                
            }, 1000);
            
            
        }
   
        
    })
    
}
function decolor(){
    options.forEach((curr)=>{
        curr.style.background="#2d035e";
        
        
    })
}
var timer = 30;
// const id = document.querySelector(".timer");

function time() {
    circle.innerHTML = 30;
    var interval = setInterval(function () {
        
        timer--;
        circle.innerHTML = timer;
        if (timer === 0) {
            clearInterval(interval);
            circle.style.color = "black";
            win.style.backgroundColor = "black";

            
            show();
        }
        
    }, 1000);
}

lf1.addEventListener('click', () => {
    clue.innerHTML = `Answer: ${arr[i].correct}`
    // lf1.style.backgroundColor = "red";
    //  clue.style.color = "black";

     setInterval(() => {
     clue.innerHTML = ""
        
    }, 4000);
    lf1.disabled = true;
})

    lf2.addEventListener('click', () => {
        clue.innerHTML = `Answer: ${arr[i].correct}`
        // lf2.style.backgroundColor = "red";
        setInterval(() => {
         clue.innerHTML = ""
        
    }, 4000);
          lf2.disabled = true;
    })




    lf3.addEventListener('click', () => {
        clue.innerHTML = `Answer: ${arr[i].correct}`
        setInterval(() => {
             clue.innerHTML = ""
            
        }, 4000);
        // clue.style.color = "black";
        lf3.disabled = true;
    })
   

  
  
  
  
  time();
  loadquiz();
  moneys();
   
  
  
